اي من الأول و أنا داري
yea from the begining and I know
تبتعد عني و تغيب
you're (gonna) go away from me and be absent
عدو يمكن إلي ترهم بس و لا ترهم حبيب
An enemy maybe to me works, bs, and you can't work as a lover
يكفي تمثيل و لعب
enough acting and playing
أنت ما تعرف تحب
you don't know how to love
كنت أحسك مثل روحي
I was feeling you are like myself
صرت بعيوني غريب
you became a stranger in my eyes
يكفي تمثيل و لعب
enough acting and playing
أنت ما تعرف تحب
you don't know how to love
كنت أحسك مثل روحي
I was feeling you are like myself
صرت بعيوني غريب
you became a stranger in my eyes
من مشيت صدقني
since you left, believe me
شفت الراحة بغيابك
I knew rest in your absence
و لا تعود ما أريدك
and don't come back I don't want you
روح و الله لا جابك
go and may god never return you
من مشيت صدقني
since you left, believe me
شفت الراحة بغيابك
I knew rest in your absence
و لا تعود ما أريدك
and don't come back I don't want you
روح و الله لا جابك
go and may god never return you
حاسب حسابي عرفتك
did my accounting, I knew you
أدري حبك ما أريده
I knew your love I don't want
لو أقول لك ما أريدك
If I tell you I don't want you
لا تعاتبني و تلوم
Don't blame me and blame
انطيتك (أعطيتك) هواية (كثير) فرص
I gave you many chances
بعد ما أريدك.. خلاص
I no longer want you, khalas
انت صح موجود يمي
It's true you're next to me
بس و لا أحسك قريب
but I don't feel you're close
انطيتك (أعطيتك) هواية (كثير) فرص
I gave you many chances
بعد ما أريدك.. خلاص
I no longer want you, khalas
انت صح موجود يمي
It's true you're next to me
بس و لا أحسك قريب
but I don't feel you're close
من مشيت صدقني
since you left, believe me
شفت الراحة بغيابك
I saw rest in your absence
و لا تعود ما أريدك
and don't come back I don't want you
روح و الله لا جابك
go and may god never return you
من مشيت صدقني
since you left, believe me
شفت الراحة بغيابك
I saw rest in your absence
و لا تعود ما أريدك
and don't come back I don't want you
روح و الله لا جابك
go and may allah not return you
آه آه آه
هو هو هو